[
    {
        "id": "01",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'てつだいます' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "手伝ます"
    },
    {
        "id": "02",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'てつだい' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "手伝"
    },
    {
        "id": "03",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'しめます' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "閉めます"
    },
    {
        "id": "04",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'けします' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "消します"
    },
    {
        "id": "05",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'あけます' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "開けます"
    },
    {
        "id": "06",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'いそぎます' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "急ぎます"
    },
    {
        "id": "07",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'まちます' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "待ちます"
    },
    {
        "id": "08",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'とまります' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "止まります"
    },
    {
        "id": "09",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'とります' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "取ります"
    },
    {
        "id": "10",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'まがります' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "曲がります"
    },
    {
        "id": "11",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'もちます' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "持ちます"
    }
]
